Kayi Tents
Gonca.
Gonca Hatun.
This doesn't look good.
Bala.
What happened Ulgen?
I saw Gonca.
She was going towards
the caged tent angrily.
I called out to her, she didn't answer.
What are you saying?
What if she does something bad?
May Allah forbid.
Don't do it Gonca.
Don't. Come on.
Oh great Allah, I am
your poor servant, Hazal.
I know I am disrespectful at times.
And I gossip from time to time.
But I have no other sins.
I swear I couldn't kill anyone.
I didn't even try to kill
that black widow Begum.
They slandered me
saying that I killed a baby.
Oh Allah.
Oh Allah, save me from this slander.
Save me, I won't gossip again.
Oh Allah, allow me to reunite with my son.
If I die...
...Bayhan will marry another hatun.
If that happens, I'll die again.
Oh Allah, please save me.
Oh Allah, save me.
Open the gate.
But Gonca Hatun..
Open the gate!
Get out.
You killed my child.
killer!
I didn't do it.
You are a murderer!
I am not a murderer.
It's a slander.
I swear I didn't do anything Gonca Hatun.
You didn't, huh?
You didn't?
The poison was found in your room.
What about what you said to Begum Hatun?
You will tell me everything Hazal.
You will tell me how you murdered my baby!
I swear upon my son..
Shut up!
You killed my baby.
I'll take your life.
I bear witness that there is...
Gonca
Mother.
-Wait.
Mother let go.
-Stop Gonca.
Let me make her pay.
No my girl. No!
Mother please let go. I
have to avenge my baby.
No Gonca. No.
I know you're in pain.
There will be a court.
Osman Bey will make the decision.
Let go Gonca.
I didn't do it.
I didn't do it Gonca Hatun.
Allah help me.
I didn't do it.
Osman Bey's coming!
Long live Osman Bey!
Peace be with you.
Surah»AI-Fath Ayat 28-29
I seek refugee in Allah from the
accursed satan.
In the name of Allah, the compassionate,
the merciful.
He is the One Who has sent His Messenger with
˹right˺ guidance and the religion of truth...
making it prevail over all others.
And sufficient is Allah as a Witness.
Muḥammad is the Messenger of Allah.
And those with him are firm with the disbelievers
and compassionate with one another.
You see them bowing and prostrating in prayer,
seeking Allah’s bounty and pleasure.
The sign of brightness can be seen on their faces
from the trace of prostrating ˹in prayer˺.
-Thank Allah.
This is their description in the Torah.
And their parable in the Gospel is that of a seed
that sprouts its ˹tiny˺ branches, making it strong.
Then it becomes thick, standing firmly on its stem,
to the delight of the planters...
in this way Allah makes the believers
a source of dismay for the disbelievers.
To those of them who believe and do good,
Allah has promised forgiveness and a great reward.
Allah the Exalted told the truth.
Orhan.
In the name of Allah.
Allah bless you!
Oh Allah show mercy to
our Prophet and his ummah.
Allah bless you.
Oh Allah show mercy to
our Prophet and his ummah.
My beys.
My sisters.
Brothers.
We only are servants of Allah...
...and breathe to spread
Allah's name and religion.
For this cause, on this path...
...we fight against our ego...
...and be a shield in front of...
...all kinds of evil with our lives.
Thank Allah...
Thank Allah accepted the actions we took.
Thank Allah, my bey.
And for this cause...
...Allah blessed us to find the
relics of Islam and take them.
-Thank Allah.
Thank Allah..
Thank Allah.
I swear...
...we will always fight with those...
...who attack our sacreds.
And as long as Allah allows us...
...we'll continue to be victorious.
Long live Osman Bey.
Thank you.
Where is it?
Where are the sacred relics, Karesi Bey?
Rest assured Vizier Hadrath.
I keep the promises I make.
Soon, you'll have the relics.
My bey.
Osman Bey's envoy wants to see you.
Let him in.
Osman Bey...
...must've heard that my
men took the sacred relics.
We were expecting
Osman Bey to be thankful...
...but he sent just a soldier.
Hadrath Vizier.
I came here...
...to give you...
...good news from Osman Bey.
With Allah's will...
...our Prophet's, peace be upon him...
..sacred relics...
...were taken in by the
leader of our nation...
...Osman Bey, Allah first.
Karesi Bey.
What are you saying?
The sacred relics...
Osman Bey has them, is that so?
If you allow us, Osman Bey
wants to host you in our tents.
He will give you the relics
himself, Hadrath Vizier.
Thank Allah..
Allah...
Oh Allah.
Thank Allah!
Osman is doing things
that are beyond his power!
What are you still
talking about Karesi Bey?
The relics of the...
...Muslims were saved from the infidels.
And you are still talking?
We need to hit the road quickly.
Safe travels Hadrath Vizier.
No!
You are coming with me too.
You will accompany me
while taking the sacred relics.
Today is a blessed day for us!
As you wish, Vizier Hadrath.
I salute the esteemed
commander of holy lands, Lucas.
It's been a long time,
undefeated Arcadeus.
Welcome.
I brought a little gift for you.
The soldiers of Magnus, who
let the sacred relics get stolen.
They would give joy...
...only when they die.
You proved your loyalty once again.
You can't watch something like this again.
Don't miss any moment.
What a great warrior, huh?
Take a good look.
Arcadeus was a slave.
He was a very strong gladiator.
No one that faced him survived.
This isn't even the best part.
Then what happened?
He became a commander
respected by everyone.
And in the end, God decided to reward him.
He is going to marry him to a...
...stupid girl who dares
to scheme behind others.
Holofira.
With you.
Son, my girl.
Don't be sad.
Those who did this to my grandchild,
those who made us go through this pain...
...will pay the price.
Orhan.
Tell me.
Begum Hatun accused Hazal Hatun first.
Then, we found the poison in her tent.
Under her pillow.
Do you think it's someone else?
To disrupt the peace?
I think we must wait a
while before the court, my Bey.
Mother.
Fatma heard it too mother.
Hazal Hatun threatened
to kill Begum Hatun.
She wanted to poison her.
But she killed my baby instead.
Father.
Hazal Hatun must die for this.
We'll be in pain...
...until we have a court, father.
We will analyze this...
...thoroughly, my sons.
Don't worry.
Don't worry my girl.
My Bey, can I come in?
Come in Boran.
My Bey Vizier Omer's here.
But...
Karesi Bey's with him.
Karadin Castle.
Fire bursting from hell...
...will explode in Karadin.
Everything's ready.
When the barrels catch
flame, the castle will burn down.
Hurry up.
Sister.
I can't keep the secret.
Hazal Hatun's innocent.
What are you saying Yusuf?
The poison was in Hazal's tent.
Holofira's server...
She's called Cecilia. She
went to Hazal Hatun's tent.
That's the truth.
Should I tell them?
Osman.
Your loved ones...
...will burn...
..like this castle.
Sister.
I couldn't protect the castle.
I failed Karadin.
They were among us.
Are you okay?
How did this happen, sister?
Who would do this?
We're going to find them.
If my name is Begum Hatun...
...then I won't die before
I find out who has done this.
Alps!
Close the gates of the
castle. No one will leave.
No one will enter.
Come on.
Sister what will we say to Osman Bey?
What?
When Osman Bey hears about this...
...he will make us pay.
Lowlifes.
Peace be with you.
Peace be upon you.
Hadrath Vizier.
-Peace be upon you.
What is it Karesi Bey?
Why did you come here uninvited?
Do you..
...want to hear what I
have to say about you?
I brought Karesi Bey here.
What do you have to say
about him Osman Bey?
First, let's sit down at the table.
We can talk about the...
...unpleasant things later.
Sit down, Hadrath Vizier.
Sit down.
Sit down..
...Karesi Bey.
Enjoy.
Thank you.
You didn't have to.
Enjoy.
But...
...for us...
...there is nothing more
important than the sacred relics.
I'm listening to you.
I came to you.
And said..
...let's look for the
sacred relics together.
But...
...Karesi Bey disagreed to work together.
I said okay.
Then...
...I thought I'd look for them alone.
But every move I made...
Karesi Bey tried to
stop every move I made.
Hear what you're saying first.
-This is an accusation.
-It is not.
It's the truth.
What are you saying Osman Bey?
Whatever you heard is
the truth, Hadrath Vizier.
Karesi Bey...
...sent his alps after me.
He made sure the monk I
caught to find the relics died.
Karesi Bey...
What he was after...
...wasn't the relics.
It was his own ambition.
So your fight for your own good...
...was greater than the relics!
Like you acting this dishonorably
in front of Hadrath Vizier...
...wasn't enough...
...you also...
...accuse the leader of the Turks...
...me, Karesi Bey.
Am I to leave your tents
where I came as a friend...
...as foe now?
The path you're leading...
...is just a path that leads
to duality and separation.
Rather than your friendship...
...your enmity is better.
Osman!
Your audacity is stepping over the line.
I was born with my audacity.
And my braveness is everlasting.
I've always said what I think is
the truth and stand by it like a rock.
Come to your senses.
Yes.
Osman Bey.
You said you have the sacred relics.
Where are they?
You can't make me marry Arcadeus.
You don't have the right.
Go and take a nice bath, Holofira.
Rest.
Get prettier.
You'll prepare for the wedding.
If you force me to marry him...
What will you do?
I'll kill myself!
Holofira.
In these lands, if
someone is going to die...
...it can only happen by my hand.
This is what you get...
...when you don't follow
orders and act on your own.
Karadin is ready...
...for hell just as you ordered.
You did well.
There is something else.
Begum hatun and his brother.
I heard them talking at Karadin.
Cecilia.
She was seen while dropping
the poison at Hazal Hatun's tent.
Incompetent fool!
Why did you do that?
Why?
The night you went to Kayi tribe...
...she poisoned Osman
Bey's daughter-in-law.
Poor woman's baby died.
I am going to take her to
Osman Bey with my own hands.
Gonca?
Oh Gonca.
Boran.
In the name of Allah, the most
merciful, the most beneficent.
Thank Allah.
Oh Allah, thank You!
Thank You.
Osman Bey.
For the reputation of the Islamic world...
...we kept a secret.
We hid it from you.
But you always talked about unity.
When you were wanting to be united...
...some people acted selfishly...
...and tried to stop you.
But...
But you did not give up.
You were ready to sacrifice
yourself and your alps.
You saved us from this shame.
Thank you, Osman Bey.
May your state be blessed.
Thank you.
Thank Allah..
...He allowed us to commit good deeds...
...and stop evil.
There is always good in the unity...
...of the Muslims, the brotherhood
of Arabs and Turks...
...and their alliance against the evil.
You...
...proved that...
...to us,
to all of us again.
From now on, our Hadrath Caliph...
...will see you as the
guardian of the Islamic world.
When I get to Cairo...
...I'll send the allegiance.
Thank you, thank you.
Send Caliph Hadrath my respects.
We are servers of Allah and the ummah.
Thank you Osman Bey.
May you and your state live long.
Live long!
What are you doing?
Cecilia.
She was guilty.
But she was my server.
I wanted to say goodbye.
May she rest in peace.
Don't let her...
...ruin our wedding.
She was a peasant.
I want my bride to be happy.
Don't touch me again.
I'd rather die...
..then to marry you.
Our love will be a tough one.
We're heading out.
Let's give Osman Bey what he wants.
But first we'll meet Karesi.
Kayi Tribe
Watch the enemy's
feet as well as their hand.
The position of the feet...
...will tell you where
his next move will be.
How will you protect yourself
from the invisible enemy?
It doesn't matter my Bey.
The heart is what matters.
Not the eyes that see.
..or the ears.
I know you're angry about our grandchild.
And you train because of it.
We haven't trained in a long time.
Attack me.
Thanks for the reminder.
I told you you'd pay for it.
It's okay as long as it's you Bala.
What's going on?
What happened to you, Begum Hatun?
Karadin, Osman Bey.
There was a fire.
The castle was filled with it.
What?
How did it happen? Who did it?
The infidels, my bey.
They hid in a secret cellar...
...and waited for the right time.
What about...
What did I tell you Begum Hatun?
Didn't I tell you...
...to take your alps with
you and go to Karadin...
...first thing in the morning
to ensure the safety there?
What did you do?
She wasted time at the
tents and wanted to see...
...the punishment Hazal
Hatun was going to get.
Then...
...wait for your punishment.
I don't understand why you
wanted to meet here, Karesi Bey.
In the letter you send..
...you asked me what I
wanted as an apology...
...because you were sorry...
...that you let Osman
get the sacred relics.
Here.
What I want is...
...this!
This is what you want?
A bridge? Huh, Karesi Bey?
Like you are done with
your reign in the sea...
...and now you want the river
in my land.
Your ships can move in these waters.
I meant compensation, not this.
I won't give you a single piece of land!
You can keep your lands.
Just give me...
...the right to passage on...
...this bridge that connects these lands.
I am the one who rules over...
...the seas among the Beys.
But Osman is the one that controls...
...the land trade.
...the merchants are...
...given passage from here...
...the distance would be halved...
...and the merchants that use
Osman's roads will use yours instead.
That way...
...while my treasure is filled..
...Osman's treasure will be empty.
And...
...that way, we will be able
to defeat Osman easier.
It's a long term, but a smart plan.
We have a deal, Karesi Bey.
But...
...after we end Osman...
...we will be...
...enemies again.
Rest assured.
Tomorrow, a trusted friend of mine
will bring the construction materials.
He will be responsible for the
security here. His name is Arcadeus.
He will get married in a
secret ceremony tomorrow.
In honor of our deal, I would like to
see you in that ceremony, Karesi Bey.
We...
...trusted you and...
...gave you the castle's
ownership after conquering it!
-Forgive me Osman Bey.
-No!
I won't.
The infidels destroyed the castle.
They are enemies.
Their goal is to attack.
Your duty is to defend.
Taking the ownership
of Karadin from you...
...would be a reward for you.
You will keep Karadin.
Your punishment will...
...be this, Begum Hatun.
With your mistake...
...the walls have been destroyed.
You will rebuild those walls yourself!
For one year...
...you won't take a
share from the taxes...
...collected around Karadin castle.
And your share will be...
...used to rebuild Karadin!
And...
...Karadin's rule...
...from now on...
...will be investigated by Bayhan Bey
and Gencer Bey, who are experienced Beys.
As you wish Osman Bey.
Kayi Tribe
Sister.
Sister what is it?
Osman Bey.
He embarrassed me in
front of Beys and Hatuns.
Bayhan and Gencer will watch the castle.
They'll investigate us.
From now on we won't make a mistake Yusuf.
Each mistake will improve Bayhan's claim.
-And now, Hazal Ha...
-Don't.
Don't.
What do you mean sister?
We know she's innocent. We must say it.
I told them it's Hazal, Yusuf.
Osman Bey won't trust us...
...if I say this.
They'll blame it on us.
And Bayhan and Hazal will rule the castle.
We'll even lose the castle.
Sister if we don't
say it they'll kill her.
You know that they'll
kill Hazal Hatun right?
No.
No I won't do this.
Our honor will be ruined, Yusuf.
What are you doing?
Bala.
Don't look like that.
I know you want to say
...'I told you so.'
I indeed do.
But despite my opinion...
...you gave the castle to her.
Yes I did.
You did...
....but Hatun made a mistake.
Is this the punishment for it, Osman Bey?
Why didn't you take the
castle despite such a mistake
No.
A single mistake...
...won't result in that.
And we talked about it Bala.
Begum Hatun doesn't feel close to us.
No.
It doesn't seem so.
Maybe you don't see it.
See what?
Begum Hatun has a close bond with Kayi.
What are you saying Bala?
Do you think so?
She does.
And this bond is so tight...
...that she gets smothered.
That's why she makes mistakes.
Such kind of bond, you know?
Baysungur.
My Bey. I followed
Karesi Bey as you wished.
I watched his every move.
I have important news.
Tell me.
What's in that cart?
I hope it's not someone from our side.
May Allah protect us.
What is he doing here?
Take your soldiers and leave.
My bey.
Byzantine commander Lucas is here.
He has a cart with him.
He wants to see you.
Let him.
Give us your swords.
Yusuf, stop. Where are you going?
I'm going to tell Osman Bey the truth.
Sister, even if you can feel at ease
with this secret I can't feel at ease.
Yusuf don't do this
brother, we'll get in trouble.
What is it commander Lucas?
What is this thing that
you say is very important?
Who is under that cloth?
You can't thank me enough Osman Bey.
This traitor whom I've killed myself...
...is the one who caused
your grandkid's death.
Gonca.
Is she the one?
Did she kill my baby?
Alaeddin.
Mother.
-Girl.
-Okay.
-Okay Gonca.
-Okay girl wait.
-I know her.
She was with Holofira. I've seen her.
-I have, Alaeddin.
-Okay Gonca.
She was with Holofira. I've seen her.
They killed my baby.
Holofira is innocent.
Cecillia's father..
...died while fighting you Turks.
That vicious Magnus used her hatred and
made her snuggle poison into your tribe.
Commander Lucas.
Come into the tent...
...and let's talk about this in depth.
Baykurt.
My bey.
Tell The Sisters..
...to let Hazal Hatun go.
As you wish my bey.
The arm of the Turks cannot be bent...
The power of the Turks never runs out.
Now that's it.
I am still young. I shouldn't
have any white hair!
I paid 5 pouches of coin for it...
...but it's good that I bought it early.
I made a profit.
Hazal Hatun's future is unknown.
I may need new jewelry.
You look good, father.
Your hatun is waiting for her death...
...and you are preparing for a wedding.
Stop talking nonsense.
When your mother comes back to me...
...I should look good for her.
Father.
If you think about my mother...
...then why did you stop us from escaping?
Either you have a different plan...
...or a different hatun on your mind.
What plan?
We couldn't challenge Osman Bey's justice.
I am back!
I am back for real!
Mother!
I am saved! I am free!
Mother, how did that happen?
My son.
I will tell you all.
My dear mother.
What's this?
I was in the dungeon and
you were shaping your beard?
It looks good.
It looks good, but...
...instead of trying to save me...
...were you thinking
of getting a new hatun?
Is that why you did this?
Of course not, my hatun.
I did it for you.
I knew that the truth would be revealed.
Mother, look what my
father bought for you.
He paid 5 pouches of gold for it.
My Bey, really?
For real, mother.
He said you deserve the whole world.
He said anything would be good on you.
My Bayhan. My brave Bey.
You knew it, huh?
I knew it, my hatun.
Go on, put it on me.
You chose nicely, father.
It's beautiful.
Father, go on.
Bayhan, aren't you doing it too tight?
Father.
It looks good.
The stealing of sacred relics.
That ignoble dog Cecilia's coming...
...to our table!
What happened in Karadin Castle...
...which is under Begum Hatun's rule.
All of that...
...was planned...
...by Magnus, huh?
Yes.
That dastard called Magnus...
...was part of an organization...
...that sneaked into the
deepest parts of the empire.
Traitors are everywhere, Osman Bey.
If you had not...
...brought that girl to me dead...
...and gave her to
me to interrogate her...
...then I would have believed you!
Unfortunately.
She threatened to kill me
when I accused him of treason.
So I had to kill her.
I assure you...
...I don't get involved in games.
I look my enemy in the eyes.
And stab them in the heart.
Fearlessly.
Like you.
If the traitor Magnus...
If you hadn't killed him I'd
burn him in the middle of Bursa.
Now, despite what I told you...
...if you still blame me for this...
...it's your choice.
I respect it.
Excuse me.
Wait.
Whether a man is...
...fearful...
...or brave...
...depends on action...
..not words.
We'll see.
We'll see if what you say is true...
...or not.
I trusted her the most.
Gonca.
How could you do this Holofira?
How could you?
I trusted her the most.
Okay Gonca hold on.
I called her my sister Alaeddin.
Calm down sweetheart.
She's the reason our baby died Alaeddin.
Gonca. Calm down.
Holofira didn't know. How could she?
She should have.
Our baby died.
I sat down next to my baby's killer.
I ate the same food with them!
Look. It's gone.
My baby's gone Alaeddin.
It's gone.
Gonca
Hold on.
You loved her she loved you.
You were sisters.
It's over.
It's over. It's over Alaeddin.
We're not friends.
She's the reason my baby died.
She's the reason my baby died Alaeddin.
It's over.
To stop our trade business here...
...and to weaken our state...
...he's working with Lucas.
True, my Bey.
Karesi Bey.
I guess you went behind our backs.
This is the second mistake.
I guess he's annoyed
about the relics issue.
He's furious my Bey.
He hits our trade today...
...tomorrow it's something else.
Karesi won't sit quietly.
What do you think?
I think this is tomorrow's business.
What will we do about the bridge?
We must talk about it first.
No trade means no money, Osman Bey.
Allah forbid, if Lucas
finishes the bridge...
...and Karesi Bey
gets what he wants...
...we can't get strong again.
They won't finish the bridge.
And we will never fail.
Tomorrow...
...the other supplies for the bridge...
...and Lucas will be
there, right Baysungur?
True my Bey.
Alright.
Gencer Bey, Bayhan Bey.
Finish preparation.
We'll head out tonight.
Orhan.
My Bey.
You're in charge of the tribe.
As you wish my Bey.
When we rain on them like wildfire...
...they will see...
...what an alliance is.
This necklace will suit...
...that elegant neck of yours...
... Begum Hatun.
My bey.
Osman Bey is going to punish
Begum Hatun because of her...
..reckless behavior at Karadin Castle.
Certainly.
That's why we're making
our move right now.
Send out a messenger.
Give this letter and the necklace...
...to Begum Hatun secretly.
Secretly.
As you wish my bey.
My bey the tradesmen you called came.
-Peace be upon you.
-Peace be with you.
Peace be upon you.
Now the era of...
...traveling for a long time is over.
The road that takes
you 40 days to cross...
...and for which you have
to pay taxes will be down to half.
Now, tell me.
Will you use my roads for your caravans?
We will Karesi Bey.
Thank you.
What will we do with this Gencer Bey?
What does Osman Bey have in mind?
Osman Bey never lets on his secrets.
Osman Bey only talks about his
moves while he is executing them, beys.
The one who thought of climbing those
walls can do anything with these logs.
Come on.
Are the preparations done?
Everything's ready my bey.
What will we do now?
We'll attack the inn
of the jackal like a wolf.
Good.
Mother, brother. This
note was on Cecillia.
It's from Holofira.
What's going oh girl?
Orhan.
That damn Lucas.
He's making Holofira
marry against her will.
Where? When? Do we know?
Tomorrow.
It will happen at the skirts of
the Monk Mountain. Mother.
Don't.
Don't tell me to stop.
I'll take care of the tribe son.
Go and kidnap my daughter in law.
It's time.
I will.
How many times have you
kidnapped Holofira, brother?
I stopped counting.
Just as how we kidnapped Gonca...
...we will get Holofira the same way.
Right Gonca?
Excuse me in this matter, mother.
I can't come with you.
You may go to that wedding...
...but it's dangerous, Orhan Bey.
It looks like you are
going to center of the danger.
May Allah help you.
Gonca.
Don't be like this, sister.
You love Holofira like your sister.
That's why...
...I feel hurt.
I lost my baby...
...and my sister.
Son, Gonca was right.
It will be dangerous.
I don't care what happens, mother.
I won't leave Holofira alone.
I am not telling you to stop.
Just be cautious.
Take your most skilled alps.
Orhan..
...I should come with
you together with The Sisters.
No, mother.
My father is not here either.
If you come with me, there
won't be anyone left in the tribe.
And as for the alps, the
fewer we are, the better.
Okay.
Lucas keeps this wedding a secret.
He must have taken precautions.
I am sending you to a
fire with my own hands.
Mother.
Pray.
I will bring your
daughter-in-law safe and sound.
If Allah permits, my son.
Look, take the best alps.
Turahan, you choose the alps.
But tell them this is
not a matter of state...
...but my personal matter.
Only the volunteers should come.
We will hit the road at dawn.
As you command, my shahzade.
Now it's your turn, Baysungur.
That dastard called Lucas must
have kept all the roads going there.
Now tell me.
How are we going to enter the wedding?
Now, my shahzade, our path is tough...
..but this is...
...the shortest way.
My mother is right, brother.
Let's say you kidnapped Holofira.
How are you going to get out of that hell?
When I...
...get Holofira from there safely...
...the rest is easy.
Commander Lucas sent your
wedding dress Princess Holofira.
-If you wish, you can deco...
-No.
Get out. I want to be alone.
Orhan.
I can't live anywhere
other than by your side.
I know it.
If you got the letter...
...you'll come to save me.
But if you can't...
...I won't live in this hell.
I'll kill him.
Even if I die at the end.
I won't marry anyone other than you.
Across the river, we'll do the
same to all watchers of the bridge.
Dastards.
The order they set up
thanks to their treason...
...will befall to their heads
like that bridge, my Bey.
True, true.
But Turk's future will be written
by men who fight the infidels...
...not those who work with them.
Come on.
No gem can be worthy of you.
But this pearl necklace out of the sea...
...is a sign of our friendship.
Tomorrow I'd like to invite you
to talk about a serious matter.
I'd appreciate it if you accept my offer.
I assure you of that.
Karesi Bey.
This was the last on my bey.
Let's go and destroy the bridge.
Let's fall down on them
like this dark night, my bey.
No.
We're going to wait.
They don't have anyone
left to go help them, my bey.
It's just the time to attack them my bey.
It is.
But Lucas will send the
rest of the stuff for the bridge.
When he brings them here,
we'll destroy them with the bridge.
They'll see what it means
to set fire to our lands.
He'll pay for it all.
All of it.
Ayse Hatun.
I'll leave for duty.
Don't be naughty while I'm away.
You are leaving and am I
staying here? I'll come with you.
If you leave what will we have for dinner?
I'll talk with Ulgen Hatun,
she'll cook something.
Ayse.
Where did you find that dagger?
Didn't I tell you not to open that chest?
Ghazi has all kinds of swords. I don't.
What should I do? Be left behind?
You always get mad at me.
It's your grandpa's dagger right?
That's why you don't let me touch it.
It is.
The son of Suleyman Shah, my
grandpa, Sungurtekin. It belongs to him.
But only two of us will know that
we belong to the Kayi bloodline.
I promise I'll get you
a sword once I'm back.
But, you have to make
a promise to me now too.
You won't open this chest again.
I promise.
Good job, my beautiful daughter.
Come on.
You make me promise so much that...
...I forget what I promise for.
Have an easy journey, son.
I'll pray for you.
Thank you mother.
Orhan Bey.
If you allow me, I want to come with you.
I know how tough those roads can be.
Thank you Ilbay.
You can come.
Brother.
I'll come with you.
I can't send you
alone in this situation.
Sister.
You stay here.
My mother needs you.
Besides...
...you can't leave Gonca Hatun
alone in this situation either.
Brother.
You're going to fight.
With only so few alps...
Orhan Bey.
I've heard that you're
going to fight for your love.
If you allow me, I want
to join you in your fight.
Thank you Yusuf Bey.
Come on Alps!
Come on Saruca, you go too!
No, mother!
I can't jump into the fire like that.
What is it Saruca Bey, are you coming too?
In a duty like this, I cannot...
...leave you alone, Orhan Bey.
I am with you.
Thank you. Come.
Thanks, mother.
In the name of Allah, the most
merciful, the most beneficent.
Safe travels, son.
So, Bala Hatun.
Aren't you going to tell me
where the shahzade is going?
She is going to bring my
daughter-in-law back, Hazal Hatun.
My girl.
Send a messenger to your father.
I don't feel at ease sending Orhan alone.
As you command mother.
Arcadeus. This is the bridge
that will drain Osman's treasury.
I want it to be finished quickly.
Turkish slaves from
Bursa were born for this job.
They should work and die here.
You are right. They deserve to die.
Thanks to this bridge,
Turks will fight each other.
Karesi will win, and
Osman will attack him.
Oh Allah!
Allah. Come on!
Damn it!
Osman!
Lucas!
I brought you hell!
Send help from the watcher posts!
Alps! Attack!
Allah is the Greatest!
You're generous, Karesi Bey.
Thank you.
But I can't accept it.
What did I tell you...
...when we first met?
You are higher than a Bey.
You're higher than a Khan.
And you deserve the best gems.
Begum Hatun.
Don't wear it for now.
But...
...keep it.
Whenever you work with me..
...whenever you decide to follow me...
...then you'll wear it.
This necklace...
...is the sign of my treason of Osman Bey.
It's the sign of...
...your devotion to Karesi Bey.
I won't give you something
and take it back like Osman Bey.
I won't embarrass you...
...in front of Beys, like Osman Bey did.
Who is Osman?
I have thousands of Beys...
...under my rule, just like him.
I'm saying...
....you can be as strong as Osman Bey.
Now...
...I have a ceremony to attend.
Excuse me.
Commander Lucas. They killed the watchers.
Damn it.
-Those barbarians will die.
-No!
Arcadaius no. They're too many in number.
Osman will burn but not now.
Later. We have a wedding to get to.
Come on!
My Bey Lucas is getting away!
Let's follow them.
No! Let him go!
He told me about the poison first.
So I'll let him live this time.
Now he's going to attack like
a dog because of his anger.
Not only him.
Karesi Bey will want to get revenge too.
We poked a hive.
The struggle has ended with this bridge.
They can do their worst.
This is the...
...part that the two sides
are closest to each other.
-That's why...Boran.
-Yes my Bey?
You will place the flying fire (Greek fire)
here and on the other side.
They won't be able to
build a bridge here again.
As you wish my bey.
This way come on. Search everywhere.
Hide now, come on.
Look everywhere.
This is the third party
we came across today.
It's a miracle we didn't
get caught my Shahzade.
That lowlife Lucas...
He prepared well because he was scared.
But fear doesn't change destiny...
They covered all the forest, my Shahzade.
We know, Baysungur.
Tell me what it's looking like.
I don't know if it works in our favor but
the priest that will wed Holofira Hatun...
...is coming this way.
How is he coming? How many
people are there Baysungur?
A horse cart...
...and some guards.
Ilbay.
You take the road.
Saruca, Yusuf.
You take the front. Go now. Come on.
What do you have in mind my Shahzade?
Gonca, I made this myself.
You don't eat anything. At least eat this.
No thank you Ulgen, I won't eat it.
Of course she can't.
She lost her baby because of the infidels.
It's not easy.
She is the devil.
She put the poison in my tent too.
So they know us well.
The traitors are among us.
Who did she come here
with? A princess or something.
She might be involved too.
Hazal Hatun.
Daughter Holofira is innocent.
Watch your tongue.
So that...
...you don't make the same
mistake Begum Hatun made.
Here, eat it Hazal Hatun.
My Gonca couldn't, so you should.
So that you stay quiet.
It's very delicious.
Thank you for the food.
Bala Hatun.
You mentioned a daughter in law.
Who is she? Where is she from?
I'll tell you Hazal Hatun.
You know her well.
The one you called the devil.
The one you called an infidel.
The one who...
...brought Cecillia into our tribe.
Holofira.
Gonca.
Daughter.
Let's talk.
Mother.
Not now.
Not now mother.
But know this.
If Holofira comes...
...then I'll leave.
What will we do Bala?
She's turning her pain into rage, Ulgen.
Keep your eyes on her.
Tough days are coming.
Be ready.
Wait.
Now!
Allah is Everlasting!
Come on!
Peace be with you, priest!
Who are you?
Tie the priest and get ready.
We will hit the road.
My shahzade.
It's not because I am afraid.
But how are...
...we going to attack a place
guarded by hundreds of soldiers?
Let's say we attacked.
How are we going to get out alive?
If you are afraid, stay back Saruca.
No, this is not fear.
It's caution.
We will go in there silently...
...and destroy everything to get out.
How is that possible my shahzade?
It will be possible.
It will be.
Now gather all the
dried herbs in the forest.
As you command my Bey.
My shahzade, what are we
going to do with the priest?
Beautiful Holofira.
Look at me.
Look at me!
In a moment, you will be my wife.
You will love this man
with whom you will spend...
...your life!
Smile a little.
Commander Lucas, Karesi Bey is here.
Let him come.
Karesi Bey.
You honored us.
I am not here for the wedding.
I am here to get information!
The relics were...
...taken by Osman.
The bridge was destroyed by Osman.
Now what's your plan, Lucas?
We sometimes win, sometimes lose.
You will either stay here and cry...
...or we will make a plan
together and finish Osman.
You choose, Karesi Bey.
Who's that coming?
One of our Alps my Bey.
Soldier.
What's the rush?
My Bey. Bala Hatun sent it.
Orhan.
What happened to my brother, father?
Lucas.
He's forcing Holofira to marry.
Orhan took a few Alps
and went to the Monk Mountain.
Saruca and Yusuf are with him.
Good boy.
He didn't leave Shehzade alone.
But Lucas...
He'll have an army ready.
Even if they save Holofira..
...they won't leave there alive.
What will we do Osman Bey?
Of course we'll go there,
and save them from infidels.
Come on.
Give me patience, my Allah!
Shehzade.
Karesi Bey is here.
When my Bey hears this..
...he'll go mad.
In the name of Allah.
Commander Lucas. The Priest is here.
Priest is here.
Get up.
Give me your hand or you'll crawl!
The sacred Priest is here.
Holofira.
Acadeius.
Step forward.
Step forward...
...so that your union can
be blessed with holy oath.
Ameen.
Welcome Great Father.
You honor us.
This couple who loves
each other passionately...
...will soon swear holy oaths...
...in front of the father.
May god give them a good future...
...and loyal children.
-Ameen.
We're ready father.
You can start the ceremony.
I'm talking to you, father.
You can start.
Have you swallowed your tongue, father?
Start it.
I didn't come here...
...to wed people...
...but to kill people.
Come on Holofira.
Allah.
Soldiers.
Come on.
Orhan.
You won't make it out alive from here.
Catch them you fools.
Arcedeus, take your men and follow them.
Kill them both.
Come on. I'm going to kill you.
How are things going in
Karadin, Begum Hatun?
There's no room for another mistake.
You know that, right?
I increased the precautions.
I've given everyone their duties.
Everything is going well, Bala Hatun.
Good.
You can be sure that...
..I will never..
...disappoint...
...Osman Bey.
If you do...
...we won't show mercy.
But you know what?
I like you being so sure of yourself.
But...
...that's the thing that makes
you do mistakes the most.
You were...
...so sure that Hazal Hatun was guilty.
Now, it's time for you to make
up for another mistake of yours.
You'll apologize to Hazal Hatun.
Ask me to do anything...
...but not this, Bala Hatun.
-I would never apologise from Hazal...
-I'm not asking.
Begum Hatun.
I'm giving you an order.
Are you going to go against my word now?
When the knights in the
castles get this message...
...they will surround the forest.
Orhan. You are wounded.
Orhan, stop!
Orhan, stop.
-Are you okay?
-I am okay.
Orhan, you are wounded,
we need to treat it.
It's okay.
It's okay, Holofira.
I got you out of there.
No wound can hurt me.
If you hadn't come...
-I was going to either kill that cruel Arcadeus...
-But...
...I came, Lord's daughter.
I am here.
My shahzade.
I don't know how, but we
need to get out of this forest.
We will, Baysungur.
We will get out and go to our tent.
Then...
...we will have a glorious wedding.
What's that?
There is smoke over the mountain.
Lucas.
He sends a signal to soldiers around.
They will corner us.
They will surround the
forest. We are cornered.
We will get out, Yusuf.
We will find a way.
...we will pave our own path!
Come on, to the horses.
Spread out! Find Orhan and Holofira
Come on, be quick!
Osman Bey is approaching
from North, my Bey.
My Bey, Osman Bey is
approaching from North.
So he is coming to save his shahzade.
Let him come.
Having feuds between us...
...harms our unity.
Begum Hatun thinks the same.
Right?
Yes.
I am glad that...
...you were freed, and
that you did not commit...
...such a treacherous deed.
-Yes, you really seem happy to me!
-Hazal Hatun.
I acted impulsive and accused you.
Forgive me.
It's not easy, Bala Hatun.
I almost died.
Forgiving is hard, I know.
Begum Hatun made a mistake.
I know it.
But people make mistakes.
She knows it.
Now, you must be the
bigger person Hazal Hatun.
Okay then Bala Hatun.
I'll be the bigger person.
This is for you.
I forgive you.
You did your best Hatuns.
Now you're excused.
That's how you are belittled Begum Hatun.
You act like you're
the mother of this state.
But I swear I'll take everything Bala.
Everything.
Your home...
..and your husband.
Shehzade.
We're surrounded by them.
They're too many in numbers.
We can't handle this many men.
Lucas thinks like the devil.
There will be more soldiers.
Over here.
Shehzade.
I'll escape them. You must leave.
What are you saying Ibrahim.
I'll ride my horse and
escape. They'll follow.
You can escape.
No. I won't let you risk your life alone.
Shehzade.
He won't be alone.
We'll go with him.
I'll go too.
Catch them.
They're coming.
Shehzade.
There's no other way.
Or we'll get caught.
Don't attack them.
We'll meet at Boz Valley after
the soldiers leave you alone.
Come on.
Don't worry, my shahzade.
We'll meet there.
Come on.
If Allah permits, we will.
Come here dastards!
They're getting away! Catch them!
Alps!
Shields!
Orhan's life is in danger.
They knew we were coming.
How is this possible my Bey?
No one knew we were coming.
Well, they know.
Treason's done in hiding
but it's revealed eventually.
We're too exposed. This isn't good.
Where are the archers?
Everywhere my Bey.
They're too many in number.
They can't make a move my Bey.
They believe that we have a lot of men.
You will pay for being stubborn Osman.
Kanyumaz.
My bey.
Tell the archers to fire
their arrows a bit further.
As you wish my bey.
My bey we have to get out of
the arrows'Tange or we'll be ruined.
Alps.
Retreat.
This way. Don't separate.
Go on then Osman.
You hurt me.
Now it's time for you to feel pain.
Alps.
They're coming from behind too. Alps!
Together, come on.
Holofira, go now.
-I won't leave, Orhan.
-Come on.
Then take this.
This is our fight.
Either we fight together...
...or we die side by side.
Don't be scared Holofira.
We'll make it out of here.
I'm not scared.
Kill them both. Attack.
Holofira.
Come on.
My bey, we're nearly out of range.
Osman was fooled by my white beard.
He doesn't know it but...
...even if the wolf gets old...
...it never leaves its prey.
Come out and fight like men.
You cowards.
We are cornered here,
there is nowhere to go!
An oppressor doesn't need a dungeon!
I swear that l am going to make the ones
who did this to us pay!
Contact us at turkision@gmail.com